export const engQuestions = [
  {
    prompt: 'Kevin: Hi! Iâ€™m on holiday here f____ three weeks. How long are you staying here?',
    answerA: 'from',
    answerB: 'fine',
    answerC: 'for',
    answerD: 'full',
    correctAnswer: 'C'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'My son saw ___ in the mirror and started to cry.',
    answerA: 'himself',
    answerB: 'itself',
    answerC: 'herself',
    answerD: 'hisself',
    correctAnswer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: '___ was a strong wind last night.',
    answerA: 'There',
    answerB: 'This',
    answerC: 'Here',
    answerD: 'are run',
    correctAnswer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'You ___ clean your teeth twice a day to avoid having problems.',
    answerA: 'do',
    answerB: 'would',
    answerC: 'can',
    answerD: 'should',
    correctAnswer: 'D'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'The campers thought they were ___ when they saw the bear.',
    answerA: 'in the danger',
    answerB: 'in danger',
    answerC: 'in a danger',
    answerD: 'endangered',
    correctAnswer: 'B'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'tender + ___',
    answerA: 'words',
    answerB: 'magazine',
    answerC: 'beast',
    answerD: 'diet',
    correctAnswer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'concrete + ___',
    answerA: 'files',
    answerB: 'proposal',
    answerC: 'builder',
    answerD: 'thrill',
    correctAnswer: 'C'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'London is the ___ city of England.',
    answerA: 'main',
    answerB: 'center',
    answerC: 'most',
    answerD: 'capital',
    correctAnswer: 'D'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'When people advertise a product, they want to ___ .',
    answerA: 'buy the product',
    answerB: 'use the product',
    answerC: 'sell the product',
    answerD: 'export the product',
    correctAnswer: 'C'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'What is the correct spelling??',
    answerA: 'necessary',
    answerB: 'neccessary',
    answerC: 'necesary',
    answerD: 'neccesary',
    correctAnswer: 'A'
  },
]
